airpush.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Airpush

**Last Updated:  April 23, 2018**

[Access to Your Information and Your Choices Regarding Our Site](http://www.airpush.com/privacy-policy/#choices)  
[Privacy Complaints by European Economic Area Member Country Users](http://www.airpush.com/privacy-policy/#privacy)

This Site Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how your information is collected, used and shared by Airpush, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Airpush”) when you visit our website at [www.airpush.com](http://www.airpush.com/) (“Site”). This Policy refers only to information we collect from advertisers, developers, and other parties that visit our Site. For information about how we collect, use and share information about consumers who have installed a mobile application that utilizes our mobile advertising services, please see our Technology Privacy Statement.

Airpush may change this Policy from time to time.  If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above, and in some cases we may provide you with additional notice.

### **How We Collect Your Data**

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Site.  For example, we collect information you provide to us when you register for a developer or advertiser account, use the interactive areas and features of our Site, apply for a job, and when you email, call, or otherwise communicate with us.

Specific information we collect: name, email address, phone number, billing address, social security number, tax identification number, credit card information, bank account information, PayPal email address, and other contact or demographic information you choose to provide.

When you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected, including:

  * **Log information:  **such as your operating system, IP address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before our Site are logged automatically.  We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Site.
  * **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:   **are used on our Site for analytics purposes, such as to understand which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Site.  You may block cookies by Airpush by setting your browser settings to block cookies.  However, if you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect our Site’s functionality. For more information on how we use cookies, visit our Cookie Policy.

We may also receive information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Site.

### **Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow other companies to provide analytics services on our behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Site, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages and links clicked.  For example, we utilize Google Analytics.  For more information on how Google collects and processes data, visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.  To opt-out of Google Analytics, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

This information may be used by Airpush to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand your activity on our Site.

### **How We Use Your Data**

We use information collected through our Site for purposes described in this Policy or otherwise disclosed to you in connection with our Site.  For example, we may use your information to:

  * Operate and improve the Site;
  * Carry out our advertising services and related operations;
  * Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Site or services;
  * Prevent fraudulent transactions;
  * Provide and deliver your products and services and to send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * Communicate with you about new contests, promotions and rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by Airpush and our selected partners; and
  * Link or combine with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

Airpush is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by United States law.  By accessing or using the Site or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the worldwide processing and transfer of information in and to the United States and other countries.

### **How We Share Your Data**

We may share the information collected through our Site with third parties as follows:

  * With third-party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work on our behalf or with us to provide the Site, and need access to your information to carry out their work;
  * With third parties that perform specific services on our behalf and may use your information in connection with the provision of such services for other companies;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, fraudulent, or to otherwise protect the rights, property and safety of Airpush or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Airpush assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
  * With your consent, such as if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide us with information.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

We bear full liability for transfers of your data to our third party agents.

Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your data in response to valid requests by public authorities or to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

### **Security and Integrity of Your Data**

Airpush takes reasonable precautions to safeguard the information we collect through our Site in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

### **Access to Your Information and Your Choices Regarding Our Site**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Airpush by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. If you have created an account with Airpush as a developer or advertiser, you may log into your Airpush account and update your information in the Account Settings section.

If you are EU individual, you have the right to obtain from us confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning you is being processed, and, where that is the case, access to the personal data and the following information:

  * the purposes of the processing;
  * the categories of personal data concerned;
  * the recipients or categories of recipient to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations;
  * where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;
  * the existence of the right to request from us rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing of personal data concerning you or to object to such processing;
  * the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;
  * where the personal data are not collected from you, any available information as to their source;
  * the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for you.

Where personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation, you shall have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards relating to the transfer.

We shall provide a copy of the personal data undergoing processing. For any further copies requested by you, we may charge a reasonable fee based on administrative costs. Where you make the request by electronic means, and unless otherwise requested by you, the information shall be provided in a commonly used electronic form.

### **Enforcement and Contact**

We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of information. Airpush is also subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@airpush.com](mailto:privacy@airpush.com), or by mail at the address below.

Airpush, Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy  
7900 E. Union Avenue, Suite 1100  
Denver, CO 80237

### **Privacy Complaints by European Union and Swiss Citizens**

Airpush, Inc. complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Airpush, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. For further information on our certification under privacy shield, visit our [Privacy Shield Notice](http://www.airpush.com/privacy-shield).

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Airpush, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Statement should first contact Airpush at [privacy@airpush.com](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@airpush.com).

Airpush, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit <http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/> for more information and to file a complaint.

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.
